Guide to GMU Public Relations Press Releases
Copyright George Mason University Libraries
- GMU Public Relations- Press Releases
  - Co-op Education Program (Box Box 6)
  - Forensics Tourney (Box Box 6)
  - Symphonic Winds Chamber Orchestra (Box Box 6)
  - Observatory Opens to Public (Box Box 6)
  - Assertive Training Workshop (Box Box 6)
  - PSA: Assertive Workshop (Box Box 6)
  - Astronomy Club (Box Box 6)
  - Forensics Victory GMU Tournament (Box Box 6)
  - PSA: "Len Substitute" (Box Box 6)
  - Christmas Concert (Box Box 6)
  - Evening Courses: English (Box Box 6)
  - GMU Jazz Ensemble (Box Box 6)
  - Burt Trip to Asia (Box Box 6)
  - Cecca Scholarship (Box Box 6)
  - Who's Who (Box Box 6)
  - Faculty Research Grants (Box Box 6)
  - American Studies Graduate Course (Box Box 6)
  - Forensics- Meg Langford Group Photo With Names (Box Box 6)
  - Andrew Miller Cutline (Box Box 6)
  - Chess Donation to Union (Box Box 6)
  - Faculty Promotions (Box Box 6)
  - GMU Nursing Award for Health Screening (Box Box 6)
  - Fall Commencement- Elias Blake Speaker (Box Box 7)
  - GMU Placement Office Announcement (Box Box 7)
  - High School Debate Tourney (Box Box 7)
  - Off- Campus English as a Second Language 1977 (Box Box 7)
  - New Faculty: CAS (Box Box 7)
  - PSA: Potpourri (Box Box 7)
  - Chess: Washington Plumbers (Photo and Cutlines) (Box Box 7)
  - Special Education Graduate Courses (Box Box 7)
  - Graduate Chemistry Courses (Box Box 7)
  - Black Named Physics Chairman (Box Box 7)
  - Charles Render (Box Box 7)
  - Faculty Display at Library (Box Box 7)
  - J. C. Wood Scholarship Awards (Box Box 7)
  - PSA: Pat Ross (Knopf) Children's Literature (Box Box 7)
  - Portnow (Box Box 7)
  - Kaler (Box Box 7)
  - Liberal Art Career Seminar (Box Box 7)
  - PSA: "The Hostage" (Box Box 7)
  - Sociology Careers Conference (Box Box 7)
  - Calendar Item "The Hostage" (Box Box 7)
  - Foundation Faculty Grants (Box Box 7)
  - PSA: GMU Information Line (Box Box 7)
  - Math Conference (Box Box 7)
  - Calendar: Dutterer Art Lecture (Box Box 7)
  - Writers Workshop (Box Box 7)
  - PSA: Modern Dance Concert (Box Box 7)
  - Dependent Workshop (Box Box 7)
  - FTP Display at L'Enfant Plaza Hotel (Box Box 7)
  - Forensics Cherry Blossom (Box Box 7)
  - Rowan Scholarship (Box Box 7)
  - Admissions: Expanded Hours (Box Box 7)
  - Music Honors: First Chair (Box Box 7)
  - Summer Session 1977 (Box Box 7)
  - Screen Writing Lecture (Box Box 7)
  - PSA: Science Night "Calendar Item" (Box Box 7)
  - On Campus Living at GMU (Box Box 7)
  - PSA: Health Fair (Box Box 7)
  - Affirmative Action Officer Appointed (Box Box 7)
  - Close Enough for Government Work (Box Box 7)
  - Dealing With Dependent Young Adults (Box Box 7)
  - Women in the World of Art (Box Box 7)
  - Cutline- Alpha Chi Donation (Box Box 7)
  - Students Direct Plays (Box Box 7)
  - Say What- Couples Communication Workshop (Box Box 7)
  - President Resigns (Background on Dykstra and Krug) (Box Box 7)
  - Feeling Fine Health Fair (Box Box 7)
  - Teacher and the Law (Box Box 7)
  - Talkers to Take Trophies at National Tournament (Box Box 7)
  - Fifth Chess Open (Box Box 7)
  - Calendar Item (Box Box 7)
  - PSA Cancer Chemotherapy (Box Box 7)
  - Talk About Winning Way (Box Box 7)
  - Media Advisory- Forensics (Box Box 7)
  - Dependents in Community (Box Box 7)
  - PSA: Astronomy Night (Box Box 7)
  - Calendar Items- Music (Box Box 7)
  - Media Advisory- GMU Day (Box Box 7)
  - Top Talkers Selected in International Tournament (Box Box 7)
  - PSA: Calendar Item- Early Music Consort (Box Box 7)
  - Workshop Will Teach Assertiveness (Box Box 7)
  - Depression Era Plays Tour, Northern VA (Media Advisory) (Box Box 7)
  - New Library Director (Box Box 7)
  - GMU Receives Rare Book (Box Box 7)
  - Search Committee Formed (Box Box 7)
  - GMU Commencement and Feature Leads (Box Box 7)
  - Calendar Item: String and Wind- GMU Summer Orch. (Box Box 7)
  - Sexisim in the School (Box Box 7)
  - Musicians Invited Summer Ensembles (Box Box 7)
  - Overseas Study Tour (Box Box 7)
  - Calendar Item- Law Related Education (Box Box 7)
  - Godwin Tour (Media Advisory) (Box Box 7)
  - FPA: Art Exhibit (Calendar Item) (Box Box 7)
  - Finding the Gifted Child (Box Box 7)
  - Calendar Item- WEEL Program, June 26 (Box Box 7)
  - Cutlines- Commencement (Box Box 7)
  - "FLASH" Auction WNVT (Ch. 53) (Box Box 7)
  - Yoga Seminar (Box Box 7)
  - Cutline- Salvation Army Plaque (Box Box 7)
  - FTP to be Videotaped (Box Box 7)
  - Summer Seminars (Choral)- Calendar Item (Box Box 7)
  - Cutline: Articulation Conference (Box Box 7)
  - Social Welfare Accreditation (Box Box 7)
  - Summer Concert (Cellists) (Box Box 7)
  - Summer Chorus (Box Box 7)
  - GMU Foundation Grants (Box Box 7)
  - Summer 1977 Commencement (Box Box 7)
  - New Geography For Teachers (Box Box 7)
  - Fairfax Rotary Scholarship- D. Pickeral (Box Box 7)
  - Fall Enrollment- GMU (Box Box 7)
  - GMU's Summer Commencement- 1977 (DeBoer) With Cutline (Box Box 7)
  - Extended Studies Off-Campus Registration (Box Box 7)
  - Gardner and Greger at GMU (Box Box 7)
  - American Folklore Course (Box Box 7)
  - New School of Bus Administration (Box Box 7)
  - New Ideas at GMU (Extended Studies Courses) (Box Box 7)
  - "S" and "L" Award to Forensics Students (Box Box 7)
  - Musicians to Perform with GMU Ensembles (Box Box 7)
  - Enrollments up at GMU (Box Box 7)
  - Auditions for Spoon R. Anthology (Box Box 7)
  - Recent Grants to GMU (Box Box 7)
  - GMU: Phi Delta Kappa Chapter (Box Box 7)
  - Affirmative Action Conference (Box Box 7)
  - Auditions for Lady Lazarus (Box Box 7)
  - PSA: Courses for Fun (Box Box 7)
  - International Education Day (Calendar Item) (Box Box 7)
  - Murray Louis Dance Company (Calendar Item and PSA) (Box Box 7)
  - Moonchildren: Scenes from 60s- Calendar Item and PSA- Release and Outlines (Box Box 7)
  - PSA- International Education Day (Box Box 7)
  - Burt to Iceland (Box Box 7)
  - Faculty Recital (Calendar Item and PSA) (Box Box 7)
  - Aging Conference "You Are Only as Old as You Feel" (Box Box 7)
  - International Education Day (Box Box 7)
  - Photographer- Slide Show (Box Box 7)
  - New GMU Faculty in Business and Prof. Studies (Box Box 7)
  - Recent Promotions at GMU (Box Box 7)
  - Parents and Professionals (Box Box 7)
  - Teaching Teachers to Teach Writing (Box Box 7)
  - Fiction Writer Beattie Lectures (Box Box 7)
  - Parents and Professionals 10-77/ 3-78 (Box Box 8)
  - PSA- Assertive Training Workshop (Box Box 8)
  - Cutlines: Student Housing- Fossil Presentation (Box Box 8)
  - Music Auditions (Box Box 8)
  - Recognition of New School of Business Administration (Box Box 8)
  - Debate Squad Win (Release and Cutline) (Box Box 8)
  - January Writers Conference (Box Box 8)
  - Spoon River Revisited (Box Box 8)
  - New Department Chairmen at GMU (Box Box 8)
  - Foreign Language Symposium (Calendar Item) (Box Box 8)
  - Books for Kids at GMU (Box Box 8)
  - Spoon River Anthology Production (Box Box 8)
  - Chamber Orchestra Concert (Calendar Items) (Box Box 8)
  - UFO's Highlight Astronomy Night (Box Box 8)
  - Economists/ USAF Management Problems (Box Box 8)
  - Novelist Teaching Spring Classes (Box Box 8)
  - A Way With Words Forensics (Box Box 8)
  - Equality in the American Work Force (Box Box 8)
  - Calendar Item: Cardiovascular Health Seminar (Box Box 8)
  - GMU Jazz Ensemble (Box Box 8)
  - Film Festival (Calendar Item and PSA) (Box Box 8)
  - TV Series: Extraordinary Ordinary: Popular Art (Box Box 8)
  - FPA Dance Concert (Box Box 8)
  - Cutline: Donation of Oscilloscope to Physics (Box Box 8)
  - Cutline- Forensics Langford and French (Box Box 8)
  - Cutline: Geography Student Trip to Baltimore (Box Box 8)
  - Interdisciplinary Courses (Box Box 8)
  - Student Art Show (Cutlines and Calendar Items) (Box Box 8)
  - TV Program Features Writing Teachers (Box Box 8)
  - Holiday Concert (Box Box 8)
  - Who's Who at GMU (Box Box 32)
  - Problem Solving for Single Parents (Box Box 8)
  - Calendar Item: Symphonic Winds (Box Box 8)
  - News Release: Chemistry 500 (Graduate Course) (Box Box 8)
  - Treasures From Dark Continent- African Art (Box Box 8)
  - Cutline: American Legion Certificate of Appreciation (Box Box 8)
  - Electron Microscope (Box Box 8)
  - Joseph Morgan- Physics (Box Box 8)
  - Music Auditions (Box Box 8)
  - GMU Leads in Employment of Scientists (Box Box 8)
  - Nationally Known Writers Give Reading (Box Box 8)
  - Japanese Nah Theatre (Box Box 8)
  - Sun Shines on Graduate English Courses (Box Box 8)
  - High School Counselors Workshop (Box Box 8)
  - GMU: Winter Commencement and Feature Leads (Box Box 8)
  - Openings in Music Ensembles and Calendar (Box Box 8)
  - Social Work Seminar (Box Box 8)
  - PSA: Courses for Fun (Box Box 8)
  - Cutline: The Otters Wheel (Box Box 8)
  - Employer's Can Find Help at GMU (Box Box 8)
  - PSA: GMU Placement Office (Box Box 8)
  - Calendar Item: Piano Trios (Box Box 8)
  - Rare Book Collection (Mycology) (Box Box 8)
  - Art Exhibit (Kravitz and Ward) (Box Box 8)
  - PSA: Financial Planing- Sally Law (Box Box 8)
  - Cutlines: Flora Crater (Box Box 8)
  - Making Money for You (Box Box 8)
  - Speaking of an Event (Box Box 8)
  - Vernon Spence (Box Box 8)
  - Education Conference 1978 (Box Box 8)
  - Black History Month (Box Box 8)
  - Women and Education (Gloria Steinem) (Box Box 8)
  - Calendar Item: A New and Different "MEDEA" (Box Box 8)
  - Teacher Education Programs Accredited (Box Box 8)
  - Oral History Workshop (Box Box 8)
  - James Dickey (Box Box 8)
  - GMU Music Auditions (Box Box 8)
  - "MEDEA" (Box Box 8)
  - Summer Session (Box Box 8)
  - Assistant Director, Extended Studies (Reithlingshoefer) (Box Box 8)
  - The Wearing O' The Green (Box Box 8)
  - Mathematics Today (Box Box 8)
  - Off to the USSR (Box Box 8)
  - GMU Meets Community Reps (Box Box 8)
  - Job Hunting? Try the Government (Box Box 8)
  - Getting the Message Across (Communication Seminar) (Box Box 8)
  - Hangups in Communication (PSA and Calendar) (Box Box 8)
  - Jazz, The External Form (PSA, Calendar Item) (Box Box 8)
  - U.S. Senator Donates Papers to GMU (Box Box 8)
  - Nuclear Energy (Release, Calendar Item, and PSA) (Box Box 8)
  - Dance Concert (Release, Calendar Item, and PSA) (Box Box 8)
  - Calendar Item: Nursing Career Day (Box Box 8)
  - FTP: Receives Gifts (Box Box 8)
  - GMU Appoints First Director Alumni (Release) (Box Box 8)
  - New President (Release) (Box Box 8)
  - Leroi Jones (Calendar Item and Release) (Box Box 8)
  - Ghosts of Indian Past (Calendar Item and Release) (Box Box 8)
  - Arts Idea (PSA and Calendar Item) (Box Box 8)
  - Master's Theses (Release) (Box Box 8)
  - Pita Bodie Release (Box Box 9)
  - Health Fair (PSA- Calendar Item) (Box Box 9)
  - John C. Wood- Scholarship Release (Box Box 9)
  - Sound of Music Release (Box Box 9)
  - Symphonic Winds Concert (PSA- Calendar Item) (Box Box 9)
  - Northern VA Writing Project Discussion (Box Box 9)
  - Craig Babcock- Mime (Release, Calendar Item, PSA, and Cutline) (Box Box 9)
  - Workshop for Counselors and Calendar Items (Box Box 9)
  - Poet Leroi Jones (Media Advisory) (Box Box 9)
  - Hagar's Children (Release, PSA, Calendar Item, and Cutline) (Box Box 9)
  - Symphonic Winds- P.V. Concert (Calendar Item, PSA, and Release) (Box Box 9)
  - Spring at GMU (Media Advisory) (Box Box 9)
  - Alvin Schorr Talks (Calendar Item) (Box Box 9)
  - Jane Elliot Film- Talk (PSA, Calendar Item, and Release) (Box Box 9)
  - Bonaro Wilkinson Overstreet (Calendar Item) (Box Box 9)
  - Book Drive Contributes Fenwick (Box Box 9)
  - Student Leaders Meet at GMU (Box Box 9)
  - Information Line (PSA) (Box Box 9)
  - Ssssh! James Dickey is Reading (PSA- Calendar Item) (Box Box 9)
  - Chamber Orchestra (PSA- Calendar Item) (Box Box 9)
  - Biology Awards (Cutline- Releases) (Box Box 9)
  - Wall Street Journal Award (Release) (Box Box 9)
  - Glen Smith- Feature Release (Box Box 9)
  - NVWP and Cutline Summer Fellows (Box Box 9)
  - Art Gallery- Fenwick (Calendar Item- PSA) (Box Box 9)
  - Pritz on Board and Cutline (Box Box 9)
  - Personal Directors Conference (Cutline) (Box Box 9)
  - Puppets- Plays- Body- Poems Release (Box Box 9)
  - Ballet Concert (Calendar Item) (Box Box 9)
  - Debate Season Ends (Release- Cutline) (Box Box 9)
  - Geography Degree (Release) (Box Box 9)
  - Local History Journal (Release) (Box Box 9)
  - James Dickey Autograph (Cutline) (Box Box 9)
  - Salop- Slates Composition Award Release (Box Box 9)
  - New Book Explores 3rd World Problems (Release) (Box Box 9)
  - Spring Graduation (Release) Feature Leads (Box Box 9)
  - GMU's Forensic Team (Release) (Box Box 9)
  - Two New Deans for GMU (Release) (Box Box 9)
  - Teaching Writing Becomes State Project (Box Box 9)
  - Police Graduation (Cutline) (Box Box 9)
  - Spring Commencement (Cutline) (Box Box 9)
  - Miss Wheel Chair Contest (Cutline) (Box Box 9)
  - Summer Orchestra (Calendar Item- PSA- Release) (Box Box 9)
  - Summer Economics Seminar (Release) (Box Box 9)
  - Retrospecting: A Dance Concert (Cutline- PSA- Calendar Item- Release) (Box Box 9)
  - GMU Forensic Team Members Receive Awards (Cutline) (Box Box 9)
  - Virginia Receives Award for Biography (Cutline) (Box Box 9)
  - Governor's Fellowships (Release- Media Ad.) (Box Box 9)
  - Allinger Receives NIH Grant to Study Hypertension (Box Box 9)
  - Summer Offers for Two GMU Professors (Box Box 9)
  - Economics Summer Seminar (Release) (Box Box 9)
  - NEH Summer Stipend (Release) (Box Box 9)
  - Addition to Robinson Hall (Media Advisory) (Box Box 9)
  - Art Gallery- Fenwick (Cutline- Calendar Item) (Box Box 9)
  - GMU Foundation to Acquire Law School Property (Release) (Box Box 9)
  - $500 Nursing Scholarship (Cutline) (Box Box 9)
  - Construction Begins on New Building for GMU (Release) (Box Box 9)
  - NSF Grants for Studies of Heat and History (Release) (Box Box 9)
  - Summer Orchestra Concert (Release- Cutline- PSA) (Box Box 9)
  - GMU Student at Edinburgh (Box Box 9)
  - GMU Professor Studies Hyper Tension (Box Box 9)
  - Documentary to Feature Working Women (Box Box 9)
  - Steinway Piano (Cutline) (Box Box 9)
  - Summer Intern Program (Release) (Box Box 9)
  - Burton's Opera (Calendar Item) (Box Box 9)
  - Kellog Grant Release (Box Box 9)
  - Bilingual Education Release (Box Box 9)
  - Summer Orchestra Concert at Student Union (PSA- Calendar Item) (Box Box 9)
  - BOV Resolution (Cutline) (Box Box 9)
  - University Courses Release (Box Box 9)
  - New Member to BOV Release (Box Box 9)
  - Summer Commencement (Release) Feature Leads (Box Box 9)
  - Novelist, Poet to Teach at GMU (Box Box 9)
  - Danforth Foundation Release (Box Box 9)
  - Learning to Communicate at GMU (Release) (Box Box 9)
  - President Johnson's Reception (Cutline) (Box Box 9)
  - Civil Service Director to Teach at GMU (Release) (Box Box 9)
  - Visiting Prof. of Sociology Release (Box Box 9)
  - Area Musicians Invited to Join Music Groups at GMU (Calendar Item- PSA) (Box Box 9)
  - Summer Commencement (Cutline) (Box Box 9)
  - Egyptian Education (Cutline) (Box Box 9)
  - African Robes (Cutline) (Box Box 9)
  - Book Donation to Fenwick, 1978 (Cutline) (Box Box 10)
  - Historians Meet (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - GMU Students Offer Part-Time Help (Release- PSA) (Box Box 10)
  - Bill Irwin (Cutline) (Box Box 10)
  - Auditions for "The Fantasticks" (Calendar Item- PSA) (Box Box 10)
  - Cultural Events (Calendar Item- Media Advisory) (Box Box 10)
  - Poetry Reading at GMU (Calendar Item- PSA) (Box Box 10)
  - Shaw, O'Neill Letters Donated to GMU (Box Box 10)
  - Congressman Harris Speaks (Calendar- PSA) (Box Box 10)
  - Gholson Directs GMU Academic Computer Services (Box Box 10)
  - GMU to Host High School Debate Institute (Box Box 10)
  - Grants and Proposal Workshop (Box Box 10)
  - Ollie Atkins Photo Exhibit (Release- PSA- Calendar Item- Cutline) (Box Box 10)
  - Academic Testing (PSA- Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Courses For the Fun of It (Calendar Item- Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Kellog Grant- Health Education Release (Box Box 10)
  - Textbook Evaluation- Release (Box Box 10)
  - New Rector Elected (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Auditions "The Miser" (Box Box 10)
  - "Working Women" Documentary (Cutline) (Box Box 10)
  - Technology Assessment- Lecture Series (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Mann Bequest (Release- Cutline) (Box Box 10)
  - GMU Presents "The Fantasticks" (Release- Calendar Item- PSA) (Box Box 10)
  - Student Faculty Lecture Series (Box Box 10)
  - Come Hear the Music at GMU (PSA- Calendar Item) (Box Box 10)
  - Humanities Conference (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - First Lady's Project (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Patriots Day (Media Advisory) (Box Box 10)
  - Two for One GMU/NVCC (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - ELCA- Conference/ Success in Schools (Calendar Item- Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Conference For Women (PSA- Calendar Item) (Box Box 10)
  - Combined Orchestra Concert (PSA- Calendar Item) (Box Box 10)
  - Harris and Herrity Debate (Calendar Item- PSA- Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Orchestra Archives (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Engineering Physics (Release) (Box Box 9)
  - Federal Register Workshop (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Tyler Memorial Fund (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Observatory Open to Public (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - GMU/ NVCC Quality at Low Cost (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Toastmistress Award/ Forensics (Cutline) (Box Box 10)
  - Visual Tek Equipment (Cutline) (Box Box 10)
  - Programs at GMU/ NVCC (Box Box 10)
  - Setting the Stage and Beyond (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Russian Educators (Cutline) (Box Box 10)
  - Hotline for Teachers (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - GMU President Names Executive Assistant (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Lecture Explores Medicine (Release- Calendar Item) (Box Box 10)
  - Careers in Music to be Explored (Box Box 10)
  - GMU Theater "The Miser" (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Career Day for Nurses (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - GMU/ NVCC (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - GMU Dance Concert (Cutline) (Box Box 10)
  - Medical Symposium (Calendar Item) (Box Box 10)
  - Professor Attends International Conference (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Langley High School Students at Atkins Exhibition (Cutline) (Box Box 10)
  - Chamber Concert (PSA- Calendar Item) (Box Box 10)
  - Science Night (Calendar Item- PSA- Release) (Box Box 10)
  - FTP Book Published (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Catch A Concert (PSA) (Box Box 10)
  - Arts and Crafts Show (Calendar Item) (Box Box 10)
  - Student Run Tutorial Service- Feature Release (Box Box 10)
  - Krug to Retire (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Children's Mural Donation (Cutline) (Box Box 10)
  - GMU Writer's Conference (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - TV Programs to Teach Teachers to Teach (Box Box 10)
  - Best Talkers to Gather at GMU (Release- Calendar Item- PSA) (Box Box 10)
  - Women's Science Conference (Release- Calendar Item- PSA) (Box Box 10)
  - Speaker Series Features Airline President (Calendar Item) (Box Box 10)
  - "Long Day's Journey" (Calendar Item) (Box Box 10)
  - Civil War Rifles (Cutline) (Box Box 10)
  - Doctoral Programs (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Who's Who Named for GMU (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - National Children's Book Week (Release- Cutline) (Box Box 10)
  - Christmas Choral Concert (Calendar Item) (Box Box 10)
  - Students From McLean High School (Cutline) (Box Box 10)
  - Facility Expansion at GMU (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Tedesco Trio (PSA- Calendar Item- Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Master's in Nursing (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Final Exam Pix (Cutline) (Box Box 10)
  - Counseling at Ft. Belvoir (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - GMU/ NVCC (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Scottish Rite Bodies (Cutline) (Box Box 10)
  - VMP Meeting (Cutline) (Box Box 10)
  - Professor Visits Argentina (Release- Cutline) (Box Box 10)
  - FTP Costumes (Release- Cutline) (Box Box 10)
  - Play Writing Course (Release) (Box Box 10)
  - Public Affairs Conference 1979 (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Alumni Day/ Mayor Award (Cutline) (Box Box 11)
  - Musicians Sought (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Display Your Musical Talents (PSA) (Box Box 11)
  - Courses for Fun (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Spring Arts Scene (Media Advisory) (Box Box 11)
  - Feminist Addresses GMU Graduates (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Musicians Sought for GMU (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Winter Commencement (Cutline) (Box Box 11)
  - Employer Can Find Help at GMU (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - GMU Plans Greater Outreach Into Northern Virginia (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - State Council Approves Doctoral Status for GMU (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Investments Seminar (Calendar Item- PSA- Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Debate Tournament (Cutline) (Box Box 11)
  - Education Conference 1979 (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Chorus Goes to Richmond (Cutline) (Box Box 11)
  - Scholars Visit FTP (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Mock Press Conference (PSA- Calendar Item- Release) (Box Box 11)
  - NVCC Art Shows (Media Advisory) (Box Box 11)
  - Poet Reads at GMU (PSA- Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - Labor Movement (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Marionette Show (Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - Long Day's Journey (PSA- Calendar Item- Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Communication Hang Ups (Release- Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - Fairfax Star Editor to Speak at GMU (Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - Nostalgia Night (PSA- Release- Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - Relations Tour (PSA- Calendar Item- Release) (Box Box 11)
  - NASA (NASA- Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - Conference on Children (PSA- Release- Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - Employer Recognition (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Law School (Release - Cutline) (Box Box 11)
  - Gloria Steinem (Media Advisory, PSA, Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - Alexandria Quartet (Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - Adam's Retirement (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Rare Photos (Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - GMU Inaugurates 4th President (Media Advisory) (Box Box 11)
  - First Doctoral Programs Approved (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Latin Bowl at GMU (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Ritual of French Music at GMU (Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - Employment Possibilities for Older Citizen (Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - Dianne Walbrecker (Cutline- Release) (Box Box 11)
  - State of the Child in Virginia (Calendar Item- Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Washington Post Writer Lectures at GMU (Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - Prize Winning Dram Black History (Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - FTP Collections (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - International Week (Box Box 11)
  - Get Acquainted Buffet (Cutline) (Box Box 11)
  - Career In Government (Box Box 11)
  - Piano Recital at GMU (PSA- Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - GMU Health Fair (PSA- Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - Poets Read at GMU (PSA- Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - L. F. Parker, Sr. (Cutline) (Box Box 11)
  - Amnesty Week at GMU (Release) (Box Box 53)
  - New BOV Member (Release- Cutline) (Box Box 11)
  - Conroy Reads at GMU (PSA- Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - Mason's Descendants (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Child Sponsorship (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Writer Visits GMU (PSA- Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - President Addresses Student Community (Calendar Item- PSA) (Box Box 11)
  - Author of Garp to Read (PSA- Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - German War Effort (PSA- Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - National Association of Psychologists (Cutline) (Box Box 11)
  - GMU's Inauguration (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Forensics Team's Victory (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Drink...Think (PSA, Release, Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - Formal Dance Concert (Cutline) (Box Box 11)
  - Dance Concert (PSA, Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - Northern Virginia History (Release, Cutline) (Box Box 11)
  - Solar Energy (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Archaeology Courses (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - GMU Inauguration Speech (Release, Cutline) (Box Box 11)
  - Writers at GMU (Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Israel Horovitz (Calendar Item, PSA) (Box Box 11)
  - Choral Concert at GMU (Calendar Item, PSA) (Box Box 11)